Welcome back to
Direct Deal after the break. Before the break, Ashi Sharma has
placed his six prospective stocks. I am placing the remaining four.
If you read the price copy of the last 10 days,
you will
see a big change in three of them, that is insurance
stocks and there was a perfect combination of buying and short covering.
Now if we
translate it on the charts, just
look at the placement of ICC Low Bar. This is the first time it has been so
strong. If you see,
after September, it tested around 1819. It reached 200.
After that, a base was created. Strong buying. It
closed above all the averages. Good
short covering. Short covering
was visible on Friday and this is the first time it has been in such a commanding position
since October 24. And
if this is not limited to just one stock,
it is visible in the entire space. So, a good move is
1948 and above it. Yes, the next supply zone
comes, it comes around 2004.
So we will get strength above 1920-1930.
After that, SBI Life  Same case
closed on your screen exactly at last due
average 200 dema and 10 dema and
closed at 1540 I think if you
hold the 1530 trajectory then it is preparing
itself for 161 as mentioned in the beginning
we are moving on the breakout of EBTA and even now I
think clusters of this range are open around 12500
and last of all again
UPL from chemical UPL had a very
strong close and closed at 551
here also flag is visible keep an eye on it and there were
good moves here along with the entire chemical
bazaar
Ashish Hichi Energy board meeting outcome
came on Saturday was preparing to raise through 44200 crore equity issue it is
not a trading stock just keep it on radar
Indian Hotels has
performed well I saw a jump of 29 in I and in
front of that increased to 351 margins improved
green curve trends  India is weak, earnings
fell to 13, beta fell to 29, profit
fell to 55, but it is a very volatile stock, bad
numbers also swing sometimes, but the
numbers are bad, it has red zone and GMR
Airports has green zone because its
December updates are good, 9 on year, 10 on year,
6 on month on month, there is improvement in December traffic,
10 on 10, talks about the whole, a small
break after the break, a
quick wrap
up of that team and